[音楽]
[music]
ピース
piece
こんばんは今日はマイクラ
Good evening, today is Minecraft
ですやばいここ最近毎日おでんしか食べてない
It's so bad, I've only been eating oden every day lately.
わ今日はセブン
Wow today is seven
のおでんでコとチア卵
oden deko and chia egg
だけえチアブってあのちくわじゃないんだ
Only Chiabu is not that Chikuwa.
ねちくわブってあれ何
What is Nechikuwabu?
持ちなべちゃべちゃしてるやつはいなんなん
What kind of person is talking about holding a pot?
だじゃ白くてもちもちしてる伝聞みたい
It's white and sticky, like hearsay.
なブですよ何ブってごめんいや知ら
It's Nabu. I'm sorry, I don't know what Bu is.
ないいやでも
No, no, but
ねちょおでんの話じゃないんだけど僕普段からうつ伏せでしか寝れないっ
I'm not talking about Nechooden, but I usually only sleep on my stomach.
て言ってたじゃん今日頑張ってね初めてえ多分なんかちゃんと仰向けで寝ようと
That's what I said. Good luck today. It's probably my first time trying to sleep properly on my back.
思って寝れたの初めてだよな今日みんな仰向けはいい
It's the first time I've been able to sleep with this in mind. It's okay for everyone to lie on their backs today.
ぞすごいね寝るの大変だったんだけど頑張って仰向けで寝てみたらなん
It was amazing. It was hard to sleep, but I tried my best to sleep on my back.
と寝起きがめちゃくちゃ良くて
And I wake up feeling really good.
かつ悪夢を見なかった夢見る時絶対悪魔見るんだよ
And I never had nightmares. When I dream, I definitely see demons.
どんな日でも悪夢を見てきたんだけど今日はね悪夢じゃなかっ
I've had nightmares on any given day, but today is not a nightmare.
た何の夢を見たか覚えてないけどいやちょっと頑張ってこれから仰向き
I don't remember what I dreamed about, but I'll do my best and turn around from now on.
で寝ようと思った
I thought about sleeping in
ねいや多分ねそうなんか寝を関係あるらしいうつ伏せはね悪夢を見やすいんだっ
Well, I guess it has something to do with sleeping. Lying on your stomach makes you more likely to have nightmares.
てそ聞いたポケモンスリープやってるやってるよ今はねイーブとゴースの厳選をし
I heard that I'm playing Pokemon Sleep, and right now I'm making a selection of Eve and Gorse.
てる全然終わんない厳選
A selection that never ends
があとすやすやが出
Later, Yasuya appears.
ないなんかポケモンスリープってうとうとすやすやぐっすりのなんか3種類に分け
Pokemon sleep is divided into three types: nap, sleep, and sound sleep.
られるんだけど寝てるパターンが大体ぐっすりかウトウですやすやがマジで出
I can do it, but most of the time I'm sleeping soundly or dozing off.
ないんだよどうやったら出るんだよすやすや
It's not there, how can I get it out?
そうだから僕炎タイプのポケモン捕まえられないんだ
That's why I can't catch fire type Pokemon.
よポケモンスリープ厳やるなんか性格とかスキル厳選があってそれによって全然ね
There's a strict selection of personalities and skills for Pokemon Sleep, and it all depends on that.
ポイントが違うんだよでポイントが高ければ高いほどやっぱレアなポケモンとかも出
The points are different, so the higher the points, the rarer Pokemon you can get.
やすくなるところに行けるし結構ね深いんですよポケモンスイープ
You can go to places where it gets easier, and it's pretty deep.Pokémon Sweep
はやっと21レベになったほお僕はね37レベだよポケモン
I finally reached level 21. I'm a level 37 Pokemon.
スリープガチ勢だからとりあえずねポケモンスリープ初めの
I'm a big fan of sleep, so this is my first time using Pokemon Sleep.
人はねみんなイブじゃなくてあのバタフリーを厳選するといい
I think people should choose Butterfree instead of Eve.
よバタフリーマジ最強だから僕最初の頃はバタフリー2体構成にし
Yo Butterfree is seriously the strongest, so when I first started, I had two Butterfrees.
てたよバタフリー2体とゴルダックとライチュとあとウィンディがね
There were two Butterfrees, Golduck, Raichu, and Windy.
最強どこの攻略サイトにも載ってないけどウィンディマジで
It's not listed on any strategy site, but it's Windy Maji.
最強ウィンディは普通ですみたいなところ結構見るんだけど僕的にねウィンディ多分
I see a lot of people saying that the strongest Windy is normal, but for me, Windy is probably the best.
ねティアゼティアSです1番
Netia Zetia S number 1
上ウィンディってスキルが他のポケモンにお手伝いするっていう効果なんだ
Upper Windy is a skill that helps other Pokemon.
けどそれがねマジで
But that's serious
最強まあまあまあということで今日はマイクラです
The strongest is so-so, so today it's Minecraft.
さてじゃ最初に企画の説明をするとえこのリスナー参加型の企画こちら僕が
Well, first of all, let me explain the project.Eko's listener participation type project.This is me.
用意したねこの真四角の土台の中に好きなように建築をしようっていう企画
A plan to build anything you like inside the cat's square base that you have prepared.
で今週で3周目になりましたさあどこまで行ったでしょうか見ていき
So it's my third week this week, so let's see how far I've come.
ましょうおいということで
Because it's Mashooi
ください僕のお花お花屋さんができましたそう僕もなんだかんだでね毎日ログイン
Please give me flowers. I've opened a flower shop. That's why I log in every day.
してちょこちょこと作ってはいるんです
I've been making it from time to time.
よこですねもこの隣の建築パクったんだけど完全に丸パクりです
Yoko Nene also copied the building next door, but it's a complete copy.
ねこのお魚屋さんの隣にお花屋さんを勝手に作りまし
I built a flower shop next to the cat's fish shop without permission.
たこれめっちゃいいブロックじゃないなんかいおしゃれなお店に使えるなと思っ
This is a really nice block, but I think it could be used for a stylish shop.
てやってみたこれガチおしゃれおしゃれブロだ
This is a seriously stylish blog.
よこれ僕の理想のねお花屋さんですなかなかいい
This is my ideal flower shop.It's really nice.
でしょということでさて全体的に見た
So, let's look at it as a whole.
けど変わったところもうだいぶなんかみんなね作れるところないなって状態に
But what has changed is that there is no longer a place where everyone can make it.
なってるでしょもう上とか作っていいからね本当に隙間を全部ね埋めるようにして
I see, you can just make the top part, just make sure to fill in all the gaps.
欲しいんだよ僕ははということであもあれ壊そうと思ってん
I want it, and I'm thinking of destroying it all.
だけど適当に作ってましたでも壊しますあれあのでかいトンネルね作ったんだけど
But I made it randomly, but I'm going to destroy it.That's that huge tunnel I made.
使い道がマジで思い浮かばないそう裏裏ルートが多すぎてじゃぱっと
I seriously can't think of a use for it, there are so many hidden routes.
見なんか増えたなみたいなところを見ていくかあいいねなんか本当にね隙間を埋め
If you look at the places where the number of people watching has increased, I really like it.Fill in the gaps.
て欲しいんだよこんな感じに
I want it like this
とか
And
おおいやこれ楽しみにしてたんだよなまだできてないなこれやばく
Oh man, I was looking forward to this. It's not done yet. This is terrible.
ない多分SCPの施設だと思うけど財団これマジで
No, I think it's probably an SCP facility, but the Foundation is serious about this.
やばいあでもなんかだいぶできてきてるエンチャント部屋だ
This is an enchanted room that's starting to look pretty good.
だいぶなんかできてきてるよねあ
Something is starting to get done quite a bit.
そうこおおこれ
That's right, this is it
はトイレ
is a toilet
だこれはおいいね
This is so nice
階段これ頑張ってんなマジ
You really worked hard on the stairs.
でここ
dekoko
はえすごうわ
The flies are amazing
すごいこれ収容違反をきてるよガチで収容違反をきてるここでビーって
Wow, this is a containment breach. It's seriously a containment breach. I'm calling B here.
やるんだねこれすごい
Do it, this is amazing
なこっちはあえいいじゃんいいじゃんいい
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
じゃん財団のねスタッフ
Jan Foundation Staff
のあいなここはねお偉いさんのねとこ
This place is a big man's home.
だよいしょいやこっから何がね使用されて
What is it being used for?
いくのか楽しみだなここはあここも資料室だえこんな
I'm looking forward to seeing you there.There's a reference room here and there.
ブロックあったんだこれパロこれマジですごいわ
There was a block, this is paro, this is seriously amazing
これ影モなしでこれだからねもこのサーバーね影も入れると
This is without a shadow, so this is also this server, and if you add a shadow,
めちゃくちゃ重くなるレベルにブロックの量が多くなってしまったからお君が作った
You made it because the amount of blocks had increased to the point where it was extremely heavy.
のかちょ上の階見に行ってみていい
You can go check out Kacho's upper floor.
かガチ作り込まれてるおおこっからかえ
It's so well made it's a big deal
えすごいななんか全部同じ感じじゃなくて1つ1つの部屋こだわりが
What's amazing is that not all rooms have the same feel, but each room has its own unique feel.
感じる案内して
Guide me by feeling
くれる見に来ただけあ案内してくれるっぽい
I just came to see Kururu, so I guess he'll show me around.
なうん白質ねええ何これえこれ
No, white matter, what is this?
何すごこんなの初めて見
Wow, this is the first time I've seen this.
たわ頑張ってんなこのダクトのところとか
They're working really hard on this duct.
すげえんなんかもらったけど拾えなかったな多分
I got something amazing, but I probably couldn't pick it up.
下の床のブロックだろう
It's probably a block on the floor below.
なほんで
In Nahon
アーカイブここまだか
Archive Komada?
なこれねワールドエリットね入れてあの僕だけ使える他の人はね使えない
This is World Elite. Only I can use it. Other people can't use it.
状態お
Condition
下ほんほんほんほんほんえ認証情報入力して
Please enter your authentication information below.
くださいピおおエントリーログ
Please Pio Entry Log
認証受け付けしました臨時サイト98の収画へようこそ
Welcome to the collection of temporary site 98, which has been certified.
すげえかっこ
Amazing parentheses
いい行ってき
Go ahead and go
ますこっから二重になっ
It's starting to double
てる
Teru
あ
a
はちょっと待って知らない後で見ようまたクソでか建築できてんだけど後
Wait a minute, I don't know, I'll see later
で見ようあれだってバックルームズでしょバックルームズもなんか日々拡大されてる
Let's take a look at that. It's the Back Rooms, right? The Back Rooms are also expanding day by day.
んだよどんどん広がっ
It's spreading more and more
てる上のなん
What's above
だ富年みたいなのができてるすごすぎるあここら辺も
It's amazing that things like Futoshi are being built here and there.
ねなるほどなるほど
It makes me sleepy
いや楽しみだなここもま他パッと見の
I'm really looking forward to this and other things at a glance.
ところこれなんかできてん
However, I haven't been able to do anything like this.
なあまだ伝説途中かな
I guess it's still a legend
いやなんかもうできてるすごい庭園みたいになっ
No, it looks like an amazing garden that has already been built.
てる声1人でやってんのかなやばいなマジ
I wonder if he's doing it by himself. It's really scary.
でよすなんか見てしまったまた別のとんでもないの見てしまったちょっと後で
I saw something like Deyosu.A little while after I saw another outrageous thing.
見に行こうあれもはあ
Let's go see it too
あいいね居酒屋ラーメン
Aine Izakaya Ramen
といやみんなワールドエディットなしでよく頑張ってる
Well, everyone is doing well without world editing.
よ頑張りすぎだ
You're trying too hard
よやばいなあえねなんか本当に000と治療の神隠しみたいなここだって前見た
This is really bad, I saw this place like 000 and Spirited Away before.
もんなここは前見て
Look ahead here
いやどんどんでかくなっ
No, it's getting bigger and bigger
てるほんでちょ上行くかまあそことか
Teruhon is a little better or something like that.
ねあで確かあれカジノカジノなんか前作ってたよねあれ
Hey, if I recall correctly, you made that casino casino before, right?
どうだろう出来上がったんか
What do you think? Is it finished?
なやってるやってるちょ後にするか
What are you doing? I'll do it later.
カジノ
casino
ここあまた何かできてるなん
Something is being done here again.
だうわあなんかちょっとエッジな会場だわ
Wow, it's a bit of an edgy venue.
スク水ここそういうお店もしてここはもしかしてそういうお店です
School Swimsuit Cocoa also has a shop like that, and this is probably a shop like that.
か座って見る
sit and watch
の
of
うわあポールダンスのし
Wow pole dancing
パン
bread
すげえこれセンシティブなお店だ
Wow, this is a sensitive shop.
いつの間にかできてるいやあれ
It was done before I knew it.
かもしかしてあれかあの僕がやったコラボでやったあのゲーム
Maybe that or that game I did in collaboration.
のすげえあであれが美術館だよねそういえ
That's amazing, that's an art museum, isn't it?
ばこちっちゃのねこれ選手見ましたあいいね家ができてき
I saw this player from Bacochcha. A nice house has been built.
てるこおしゃれなねお家これ見てないかも
Teruko's stylish house. Maybe you haven't seen this.
なホテルグランシニなシニなあ427僕の誕生日
Na Hotel Grand Shini Na Shini Naa 427 My Birthday
ねお
Neo
おしゃれあこれいいじゃんバイキングだいやっぱパン
Stylish things are great, Viking Daiyappa bread
よこの景色あれ怖い
That scenery outside is scary
なじゃホテルの部屋もあるかな
Is there a room at Naja Hotel?
お地下も
Underground too
あるいやプール欲しいなあ作ってる途中
No, I want a pool, I'm in the process of building one.
だこお邪魔しますおおこれ
I'm bothering you, this is it
レストラントこっちの方が高級感あるなこのは
This restaurant has a more luxurious feel.
おこっちは初見です切抜から来ましたいらっしゃい
This is my first time seeing you. I came from a clipping. Welcome.
今見てます今週分を見てい
I'm watching this week's edition.
ますここまだかいやせっかくならプールも作ってほしい
I'd like to build a pool if I can stay here.
ないいぞあれこれカ
No, this and that
道楽すごいウィザースケルトンの頭はになっ
The head of the awesome wither skeleton is now
てるこれすごくねこれや
This is amazing.
ばカ道楽だ
It's a stupid hobby
ウニや
Sea urchin and
ばクオリティ高ライブ来た
A high quality live show came.
スターリーできたかなあ工事中あでもなんか形になってき
I wonder if Starry was made.During construction, things are starting to take shape.
てるすげえ楽しみ
I'm really looking forward to it
だほんであも見てないかあいやあれ見た
Didn't you see Amo in Dahon? I saw that too.
かここ
Kakoko
ねほん
Nehon
であここも追加され
So this is also added
たこの中華スタイルの
octopus chinese style
ねおいいじゃんいい
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
じゃん
Jan
ああオンリーアップ感あるやばなんかいろんな建築がある
Ah, there are many kinds of architecture that have a unique feel.
から結局僕オンリーアップやってないもん
After all, I didn't do Only Up.
なお畳の部屋も
There is also a tatami room
あるいいねああな
That's nice.
おおここうなってるだけかなるほど
Oh, I can see how it's just growling here.
ねもう売ってないしな僕ね買ったんだよ販売しなくなったその日に買ったんだよ
They don't sell it anymore, so I bought it the day they stopped selling it.
めっちゃ運良くない販売停止の日に買っ
I bought it on the very unlucky day when sales were suspended.
た
Ta
おおなんか怪しげなここ何かあるぞこれ裏に何かある
Oh, there's something suspicious here. There's something behind this.
ぞほらあだ
Zohoraada
けど先は行けないなここまで
But I can't go any further.
かいや隠すからなうちのリスナー隠すからねどこに何があるか分からないん
I'm going to hide it. I'm going to hide my listener. I don't know where anything is.
だ
is
よいずれはこうやってあの徒歩で行けるようにしたい
I want to be able to go there on foot someday.
ねこれ行けないやん徒歩
I can't go, I'll have to walk
で徒歩で全部行けるようにしたい観光用にこのセーブデータを公開する
I'm releasing this save data for sightseeing who wants to be able to go all on foot.
予定だから一般の人が入れるよう
It's scheduled so the general public can enter.
に
to
おおここはあ
Oh this is here
出れるでここずっとあるけど未だ内装はないんだよ
It's been here for a long time, but there's no interior yet.
なこっちはと
Nakocchihato
かなんかさっきでかい城みたいの見えた
I saw something like a huge castle just now.
けどん3Dスタジオ
Ken 3D Studio
おお
oh
すごい3Dスタジオ
amazing 3d studio
だここでみ切り抜きができるよグリーンバッグで
You can cut out only here with a green bag.
これ
this
すごいこれ面白い
Wow this is interesting
ねで登れるスペ
A space where you can climb with a ne
ん商店街なんかあるな
There's a shopping street.
おおできてるできてる松屋あ松屋だ
Oh, it's done, it's done, it's Matsuya, it's Matsuya.
すごなんか松屋入って30秒で家なんかご飯食べて出るみたいな動画見たなこの
I saw a video of someone walking into Matsuya and leaving after 30 seconds of eating something at home.
前わいいこういうロジ裏いい
The front is cute, this kind of logistics is nice behind the scenes
なこういうのよ求めてたものを
This is what I was looking for
怖い
scared
なフィギあれ
That's a figure
ねなるほどねこれぞクーロンて感じするよ
I can't help but feel like this is Coulomb.
ねよし
Neyoshi
よしあはいはいはいはいシャッター
Okay, yes, yes, yes, shutter.
ガこういうのこういうのもっとこういうねところ隙間埋めていい
You can fill in the gaps with things like this and more like this.
んだからねみんなどんな建築でもいいからだってあれ
That's why it doesn't matter what kind of architecture you want.
がいるぐらいだよ安全
It's safe enough that there are
大地ほんじゃあカジノ見に行くか
Daichi, do you want to go see the casino?
カジノでカジノ見
See the casino at the casino
たら真ん中行って今回紹介してくれる人のところ行く
Then go to the middle and go to the person who will introduce you this time.
かあ待って上もある
Oh wait, there's one above too
な宇宙人だあ捕まってるとれのろ捕まっ
It's an alien! They're being caught.
てる宇宙人にってる
It's like an alien
よどうやって入るんだこれ
How do I get in here?
抽選入れないの
I can't enter the lottery
かこれ雲かな雲の家だ
Is this a cloud? It's a cloud's house.
なこれ見るかいやここやばいよ
What are you looking at? This place is dangerous.
なよくやったよ
Well done
お来たあバニーになってる僕は先週バニーにしろって言ったから
Come on, I'm turning into a bunny because last week I told you to turn into a bunny.
バニーヌになってるさて紹介してもらおうかなじゃあ
Now that I'm Vanine, I'd like you to introduce me.
えコイン遊べんのこれで本当にこ真ん中
I can't play Ecoin, I'm really in the middle of this
何いやこれマジすごいよ
What, this is seriously amazing
なえルーレット遊び方ガイドブックがあるこれ
There is a guidebook on how to play Nae Roulette.
ルーレットえ黄色い箱にコインを入れて中心のボタンを押すとスタート当たれば紫
Roulette: Put a coin into the yellow box and press the center button to start. If you win, the game will turn purple.
の箱に入れた数の2倍の
twice the number you put in the box.
え黄色い箱にコインを入れるあなるほどなるほどで紫じゃどうしよっかなえ本当に
I see, I put the coin in the yellow box, but what if it's purple? Really?
じゃここにしよっかな
I guess I'll do it here then.
じゃあ32個よし行くぜスイッチ
Okay, let's go with 32 switches.
オンすご
On amazing
は僕のコイはあなくなっ
My carp is gone
たもう1回16個だ
Just one more time, 16 pieces.
来いは全然当たんないこっちが多いのなんか
I guess there are a lot of people who don't get it right at all.
こここれ
here this
な
Na
はい惜しいうわ
Yes, it's a shame
惜しい全然当たんねいやでもここばっかな気するここ
It's a shame, I don't get it at all, but I feel like this is the only place here
とこことこの3つかけにしようこ3
Let's put this and this three together 3
ね[音楽]
Hey [music]
け来当たった
It came true
あれお支配人金ないぞ僕の金
That manager doesn't have any money, it's my money.
返せえ違っ
I can't give it back
たおなくなっちゃっ
Tao is gone
たコンないよもう1個強えたん
I don't have any octopus, I just bought one more
かバグかもいやすごい
Or maybe it's a bug. That's amazing.
よこれはあ換金所だふわもらっ
Yo, this is a money exchange place.
とこう
Toko
すごいスロット
amazing slots
エリアあこれいいねバーも
There are also nice bars in the area.
あるわいいななんかMMOやりたくなるねこういうの見るとスロット
It's so nice that it makes me want to play an MMO.When I see something like this, I want to play slots.
えまさかこれもできんのこれも遊べる
Oh no, I can't even do this. I can play this too.
じゃあえ1個あえ当たった
Well, I managed to win one.
すごいよった1
It was amazing1
個これダなんねえこれやばくない
This is no good, this isn't bad.
はいこだねごめん壊しちゃったやばい壊しちゃった
Yes, I'm sorry I broke it, I broke it.
大丈夫かこれこし
Are you okay?
てあやばい私治った配にごめんシルカボックス
I'm sorry, I'm healed, Silka Box.
壊しちゃった開けられなくなってた
I broke it and couldn't open it.
えこれ大丈夫
Well, it's okay
あありがとうよし8コインあはは来
Ah, thank you, 8 coins.
たすげえ22個もらえ
Receive 22 Tasugee
たこれめっちゃ面白い
Takore is really interesting
じゃんこれ一生コイン稼げるな
Well, you can earn coins for the rest of your life.
えなんか確定演出みたいな出たのやばくない
It's not bad that it came out as if it was a confirmed performance.
ナイス何これこれの完成度高すぎ
Nice, this is so perfect.
でしょえまだ他にわ作ってる予定だなえこれ何これ
Right, I'm still planning on making something else. What is this?
は
teeth
えあはははは
Eahahahaha
はいはいピンボールだはいこれむずいって
Yes, yes, it's pinball. Yes, this is difficult.
これ2人でやりよだはいはいここ面白い
Let's do this together, okay, this is interesting.
なてかこの浮は何この浮は何マジで
What is this float? What is this float? Seriously?
はいはいあ真ん中ばっか行くんだけどはいよし
Yes, yes, I'm only going to the middle, but okay.
よし
Okay
まずはいはいはいはいちゃんとやんなきゃ跳ね
First of all, yes, yes, yes, I have to do it properly.
かえないなはいはいはいはい
I can't change it, yes, yes, yes.
はいはいや
Yes yes no
ばこれでもなんかあれかコインもらえるとかはない
Even if you do this, you won't get any coins or anything.
か[音楽]
ka [music]
これ天才
This is genius
でしょすごいなこれマジすごいないや
That's amazing. This is seriously amazing.
回路カロくめの本当に尊敬する手札手札
Circuit Karokume's hand that I really respect
へこれは何あルールブックだポカ来た足元のボタン押すとカードが1
Hey, what is this? It's a rulebook. When you press the button at your feet, you get 1 card.
枚右えっと青い箱に入りますふんふんふんボタン順番に押してください複数箇所同時
It will go into the blue box on the right.Press the button in order.Multiple places at the same time.
に押すとうまく動かないかもカード交換は左の赤い箱にカードを捨ててその枚数分
If you press it, it may not work properly.To exchange cards, discard the cards in the red box on the left, and then press the red box on the left for that many cards.
またボタンを押してください遊び終わったらカード
Please press the button again. Cards when you are finished playing.
を全て赤い箱に入れてテーブル上のレバーでシャッフルして何秒か経ったらレバーを
Put them all in a red box, shuffle them using the lever on the table, and after a few seconds, press the lever.
切って右のレバーを5秒ほどオンにしてください山札切れでカードが出ない
Turn it off and turn on the lever on the right for about 5 seconds.The deck is out and no cards come out.
はふはふ正面手前の足元ランプが切れている時もどの手順でカードを山札に戻せ
Hahahaha Even if the foot lamp in front of you is out, use any procedure to return the card to the deck.
ますほんほんほん
Masuhonhonhonhon
えっとまずこれか
Well, first of all, this?
ほ
Ho
でこん中にはいスペードの2スペードの
2 spades in the middle of the spade
2でえ何枚だっけポーカーって[音楽]
How many cards are there in 2 poker? [Music]
ポカって何枚もう1
How many Poka are there?
回5枚か25枚オケーオケ
Okay, okay, 5 or 25 times.
オケあてない
I can't find the orchestra
な1
Na1
枚あ来たえっとクラブの2
Shea Akita Ert Club 2
あ違うダイヤ
A different diamond
かまだかなほいクラブの
Kamada Kanahoi Club
5クラブの4いやちょ弱い
4 of 5 clubs is weak
な
Na
2245ああ8とえじゃ2枚残しで3枚捨てしよう
2245 Oh 8 and Eja, let's discard 3 cards leaving 2.
か3枚捨てオーでえ3枚捨てした状態でえっとその枚数分ボタン
Or discard 3 cards and press the button for that number of cards with 3 cards discarded.
押す枚数分ボタンを
Press as many buttons as you want to press.
押しこの真ん中のボタンでいいの3回トントントンあいいのか
Is it okay to press the middle button three times?
1223これで来んのか来い
1223 Are you coming here?
あ来たこれ
Oh here it is
は2ペア2ペア
is 2 pairs 2 pairs
ですツペア
Desu pair
だやっ
Yay!
たあ弟配人はこれはジ
My brother's guardian is this
かあここにあるんだえ面白あごめんこう
Hey, it's here. It's interesting.
かどうだこれ僕の勝ち
No matter what, this is my victory
か僕の勝ちだあこれ4人でできるん
It's my victory. Four people can do this.
だ
is
で終ったら壊して返すの
When you're done, break it up and give it back.
か終わったら入れ
Put it in when finished
て何秒か経ったらレバーを切って右のレバー
After a few seconds, turn off the lever and press the right lever.
12345入れてで
Put 12345
えっとどっちだ
Well, which one?
左ここでシャッフルし
Shuffle left here
てシャッフルされてる何秒か経ったらレバーを切ってでえっと右のレバーを5秒
After a few seconds of shuffling, turn off the lever and press the right lever for 5 seconds.
ほどにする
Moderate
1345これで終わりとえこれマジでおもろいねいやすごい天才だ
1345 This is the end. This is really interesting. What a genius.
よすごいな1週間でみんなゲームを1234つ作ったよ今のとこいやすごいよ
Wow, everyone made 1234 games in one week. So far, it's amazing.
期待してるよこれから1週間で4つ作ったんだよゲームやば
I'm looking forward to it. I've made 4 games in a week. That's awesome.
いって多分なんかRPGスクールとかでやる
I'll probably do it at an RPG school or something.
よりむずいよこのマイクラのゲームはこれややばいな天井とかも凝ってるし仕事がね
This Minecraft game is more difficult than this, with its crazy ceilings and complicated work.
早すぎる
too fast
おお化けが化けが
Oh ghost, ghost
いるえじゃあ紹介コーナー行きますかあいやちょっと待ってその前
Okay, let's go to the introduction corner. Wait a minute, before that.
にあれを見に行こう先週僕がね作ったデジタルサーカスのね土台をねちょっと
Let's go take a look at the foundation of the digital circus I created last week.
別のリスナーさんが引き継いでくれたんだよそれ見に
Another listener took over, check it out.
行こううお屋根ができてるこのね土台と壁だけは僕がやったんだ
Let's go, the roof is done. I only did the foundation and walls.
けどちょ楽しみにしてたんだよえあ待って両側も作ってん
But I was looking forward to it.Wait, I'm making both sides too.
じゃんじゃ見に行きますか
Are you going to see Janja?
うおーすげえ天井やばよくやったな僕この周りの
Wow, you did a great job on the ceiling.
壁は僕だけワールドエデト使えるからそれでやったけど天井だって1人でポコポコ
I was the only one who could use World Edit on the walls, so I did that, but the ceiling was also pokopoko by myself.
やったんでしょこれ1週間でやったのやばすぎ
You did it, you did it in one week, it's amazing
でしょああれはまさかポモあ待ってレットも
Wait, Rhett too.
あるやば再現度高高すぎ
The reproducibility is too high
でしょほんまにこれワールでこれね出口
This is the world and this is the exit.
と
and
すげえでもさこれ多分左左右行けるってことじゃあれだ
That's amazing, but it probably means I can go left and right.
これまさかさこの位置は部屋を作ったってことじゃないの
I didn't expect this to mean that a room was created in this position.
かこれ部屋作ったでしょ
Did you make a room?
うすげえすげえこれマジでえあ1人1人ちゃんと作っ
It's so thin, it's so amazing, it's serious, each and every one of us should make it properly
てるどこだっけあここまさか
I wonder where it is?
ああバグってるや
Oh there's a bug
ばすごいあなるほどねこれエドクリスタルで目を表現したん
That's amazing, I used Ed crystal to express the eyes.
かえ他のこの部屋とかあ多分これ予想で作ったんか
Kae: I guess this other room was made based on a prediction.
な多分これ全部予想でやったでしょ
Maybe you predicted all of this.
すご再現度高
Amazing reproducibility
すぎやばいステージのところとかやばいもん
Sugiyabai stage and other things
なザアメイジングデジタル
Naza Amazing Digital
サーカスやばいやマジ任せてよかったあこれはこれ
The circus is crazy, I'm glad I left it to this.
はこれね最後のシーンだね口ぐにゃーのとこ
This is the last scene, where the mouth is limp.
ね口ぐにゃーのシーンのとこだよさて座ってるえ
This is the scene where Neguchi is squishy. Now, sit down.
[音楽]すごこれ何かの最これはねYouTube
[Music] Wow, this is the best YouTube
でザアメイジングデジタルサーカスで検索すると出るなんか3Dアニメーション今
If you search for The Amazing Digital Circus, you'll see 3D animation now.
すごいよ3週間で1億再生ぐらいされてるやつなんだ
That's amazing, it's been played about 100 million times in 3 weeks.
けど可愛いアニメとちょっとバックルームズとかSCP混じっ
But it's a mix of cute anime and a bit of Back Rooms and SCP.
てるようなホラー要素のある不気味な作品なんだけどうちのリスナーさん多分みんな
It's a creepy work with horror elements, but my listeners probably all
好きだよいやすごいなえじゃあれも作ってほしい
I love it, it's amazing, I want you to make that too.
わこの出口の先出口の先
Beyond my exit, beyond my exit
させっかくだからこっち来てここの入口に繋がるように
Please come this way and connect to the entrance here.
してよこっから一応ね僕がねやろうとしてたのはねほら
Well, that's what I was trying to do.
そこに待てかここら辺から繋げてちょっとか頑張って僕も手伝う
Wait there, connect from around here, do your best, and I'll help too.
けどそこのサーカスまで行くまでちょこ頑張って繋げよう
But let's try our best to connect until we get to that circus.
あのオフィスのところをマが言ってたから見てけどめっちゃ
Ma told me about that office, so I looked at it and it was amazing.
面白かった面白いしよそうなんだよみんな好きかなと思ってた
It was interesting, it was interesting, and it looked good. I thought everyone would like it.
けど頑張ってここね繋げるんだこことかさこうなってる
But I'll do my best to connect this place.It's like this.
かまどっかね行けそうなところあったら繋げよう
If there's a place you can go to, like a furnace, let's connect.
いや作業大変分かるマジ大変だ
No, I understand that the work is really hard.
よしじゃあ消化タイムに入ります
Okay, now it's time for digestion.
か今は僕がねざっくり見てなんか新しいの増えてるかなで見たやつだけどこっ
Well, I've just been looking through it, and I wonder if there's anything new.
からいやここに実はあるんすよみたいなのがあっ
Well, there's actually something here.
たら来て
Come on.
くれえこれサーカスだよねあそうだね多分このはサーカスだよ
Give it to me, this is a circus. Oh yeah, it's probably a circus.
な真っ白なんだおじゃあ連れてってもらおうか
It's all white, so why don't you take me with you?
ないい
Not good
よプールありますよどこあのさっきのホテルの
There's a pool at that hotel.
ところつい
Tokoro Tsuki
てこう空を登っていくえけどあ
I'm climbing up the sky, but
た登れ登れ新しい成功もあ増えてるかもう成功
Climb, climb, new successes, are they increasing?
マートはいいよ成功マートめっちゃ増え
Mart is good, the number of successful marts has increased tremendously.
てるあホテルえ
Terua Hotel
どここっち上
Where is this top?
か見てなかっ
I didn't see it
たやっぱホテルと言ったらプール
When you think of a hotel, you think of a pool.
でしょえあこの
Isn't that right?
先安全プールもう落ちない
I won't fall into the safety pool ahead.
おお落下事故発生忘れない誰かなくなっ
Oh, I won't forget that a falling accident happened. Someone disappeared.
てるあプールだあえ何これ
It's a pool. What's this?
ガチプール
Gachipur
じゃんこれいい
This is good
なでもなんかあれだなちょっと怖いなお地蔵さんとか置いてある
There's something a little scary about that, like a Jizo statue.
プール怪しさ満点[音楽]
The pool is full of suspiciousness [music]
のなんで後ろ側こうやって塞がれてん
Why is the back side blocked like this?
のいやもっとでかい
No, it's bigger
プール欲しいなこういうの作れるならそれこそなんかあのある
I want a pool.If I can build something like this, it's something like that.
じゃんサマージャンボじゃなくてなんて言うんだ子供用のでかい
What do you call it, not Summer Jumbo? It's a big one for kids.
プールどっかもうでも
Anywhere in the pool?
スペースいやでも意外とあるよみんなまだまだあるから
I don't want space, but there's more than you might think.
作ろう次な
Let's make the next one
方サマーランドそうサマーランドみたいなサマーサマージャンボはあれ
Summerland, yes, Summerland-like Summer-Summer Jumbo is that.
だ宝くじだあもういないもしかして
It's a lottery. Maybe it's gone.
コシブ終わりあいるあ来た来た来た来たあれあでも君確か
I'm sure you're here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm sure it's the end
SCPの人だよねSCP財団まだ
You're an SCP person, right? The SCP Foundation isn't here yet.
あるまだ何かあるよう
I think there's still something
だこの中あ美術館新しい展示品があるオオケオ
Dako Nakaa Museum of Art has new exhibits at Okeo
オッケーああ来たよみんな作りたい人募集後ろに
Okay ah, I'm here. Everyone is looking for people who want to make it. Behind the scenes.
廊下をつなげて好きに作ってくださいこれみんな作って
Connect the hallways and make it as you like. Make this everyone.
くださいこの財団施設ね伸ばして宣伝でしたありがとういやわかんねえな
Please, this foundation facility was expanded and advertised. Thank you, I don't understand.
でも確かにあそこじゃなくてもっとここら辺に看板置いといた方が
But it would certainly be better to put more signboards around here instead of over there.
良かったんじゃないかいいな僕もなんか
I guess it was good, I guess so too.
作ろう皆さんも自信ある方SCPの財団施設を広げ
Let's build it If you are confident, expand the SCP foundation facilities.
ましょう宣伝でし
Let's advertise it.
た次の方
The next person
どうぞえなんかさっきでかい建物
Go ahead, that big building you just saw.
あいあれつい
Ai Aretsuki
てこうん
Tekouun
あのポールダンスのところの
That pole dance
人あしたえここってさいや見なかったっ
I didn't see anyone here tomorrow.
けここここ見た気がするぞ増え
I feel like I've seen a lot of them
たこれ怖いBGMだしこのね声見たな
This is scary BGM and I saw this voice.
ピアノ配信紹介してなかったっ
I didn't introduce piano streaming.
けこの謎のくりにね繋がれてるここマジ雰囲気いいな
The atmosphere here, where Keko is tied to a mysterious chest, is really nice.
いや何かあるのか降りる
No, I'm going to get off if something happens.
かあ紹介してなかっ
I haven't introduced you.
たこれ
Takore
[音楽]はまでもこんな感じかあしてなかった
[Music] has never been like this before.
じゃあ僕多分ね1人で見たんだこれすごいよ
Well, I guess I saw it by myself. It's amazing.
ねこういう謎空間僕大好きだからえだから僕ねこれ見
Hey, I love mysterious spaces like this, so that's why I'm watching this.
てあれ作ったんだおおありがとうこれ見ていや僕もなんか真似し
I made that, oh thank you. Look at this, I copied it too.
ようって思って作ったんだ
I thought so and made it
よこ作ったのは
What I made next is
[音楽]あれどこ
[Music] Where is that?
だどこだちょっと待ってあれ
But wait a minute.
だこれ
This is it
ねあの空間見て僕もなんか真似して真っ白の空に赤い
Hey, when I look at that space, I try to imitate the pure white sky and red.
扉作ったんだ
I made a door
よサイバーパンクみたいでしょそうなんだ[音楽]
It's like cyberpunk, right? [Music]
よよしそれでは次の[音楽]
Alright then, next [music]
方BGMねなんかマイクラ曲全何種類みたいなやつを流し
The BGM plays something like how many different Minecraft songs are there?
てる今日は意外とあれか紹介税がいない感じか君は紹介の人
Surprisingly, there is no referral tax today.You are the person who introduces me.
か違うっぽい[音楽]
It looks like it's different [music]
な紹介する
Introducing
制作者じゃないけど中華建物の裏側の壁の奥にあるえそうなんかでかい城みたいの
I'm not the creator, but it looks like a huge castle behind the back wall of the Chinese building.
あったやつだよねあどうやって行くんだろうあついてこうか
That's right. How do we get there? Shall we go?
な
Na
向こうまあとそう作りかけの人も多いしな
There are a lot of people over there who are still working on it.
[音楽]上に何があるんだああのUFO
[Music] What's up there, that UFO?
[音楽]かこれ
[Music] Kakore
ねこっから入るあ並んでる頭
A row of heads coming from a cat
がこのこのUFOのコンセプトは何あ
But what is the concept behind this UFO?
すごいどっから入っ
Amazing where did it come in?
たこの宇宙人といい頭光ってる
The octopus's alien head is glowing
けどこれこれのコンセプトが謎あでも内装
But the concept of this and that is a mystery
いい長の
good length
ね教会も制作者ですがミニストーリーがあるので美術館の後によければ案内します
Nekyaku is also the creator, but there is a mini story, so I'll show you after the museum if you'd like.
コメントでは分かりづらいかと思うあそっか美術館なんか言ってた
I think it's hard to understand in the comments, but you said something about Asoka Art Museum.
なそこね宇宙人のコンセプトのやつを見て
Look at that alien concept thing.
から
from
おおなるほど
I see
それ出てるぶわんブワブワンって出てる君ぽいから作っていただけですなるほど
It looks like you, so I just made it. I see.
上の奴らが上の奴らがなんかね可愛く
The guys on the top are kind of cute
てUFでもねやっぱ上は金未来系が多いと
Even in UF, there are a lot of Kim Mirai types at the top.
嬉しい
happy
なあこんなでかかったっ
Hey, it's this big!
けで美術感があれか美術感も最初分かりづらかったからな
It was hard to understand the sense of art at first.
位増えた
increased in rank
らしいさて
Apparently now
小羊のための特別室
special room for lambs
あ献金できるよここでお金も入れて
Oh, you can donate money here too.
あるえこれ見たやつ僕あ2023年11月9未名展示室にて
Yes, I saw this.November 9, 2023, in the unnamed exhibition room.
遺体が見つかりましたそはの調査により明らかとなり大きな話題をびましたトカは
Toka's body was found and the investigation revealed it and it became a hot topic.
この小さな芸術家が己れのむを展示室に残すに至った心情を試みえ鏡遺体の処理
Try to understand the feelings that led this small artist to leave Renomu in the exhibition room. Disposal of Kagami's body.
ごも何性の老性のレプリカにて当時の状況を保全することとしまし
We decided to preserve the situation at that time with a replica of Gomoji's old age.
た人の死というデリケートな事情であるため干渉ななされた方に不快感をもたらす
Because the situation is a delicate one, such as the death of someone who has died, the interference may cause discomfort to the person being interfered with.
可能性もございますがなりとぞご用しいただければ幸いですまたトカを運営して
Although there is a possibility, I would appreciate it if you could use it.
おります空論財団では今後同様の地帯が起きることを防ぐべく個基金を設立しまし
The Kuron Foundation has established a private fund to prevent similar areas from occurring in the future.
た危険の寄付献金は右の喧嘩箱にて同時に受けつけておりますなお本件の権威につき
We are accepting donations at the same time in the fight box on the right. Regarding the authority of this matter,
ましては飯のYouTubeチャンネルにて公開されております
Moreover, it is published on Mei's YouTube channel.
ああ
ah
ありがとうじゃ金入れとくか30
Thank you, I'll put some money in.30
コインさてえでもこれとは別に増えたってこと
Coins have also increased separately from this.
でしょこれじゃね夢で見た
Right, this is what I saw in my dream.
部屋
room
まさか夢にやこれあれかあの子の部屋か名前が出てこ
I never thought my name would appear in my dreams, this or that, or that child's room.
ないスイッチの子えあ
No switch child eh
まさか
No way
うおおうだなるほどねこうやって表現したのか
It’s so amazing, how did you express it like this?
めっちゃいいじゃんあポ
That's really good Po
ニコでもこれも確定なんだねスイッチ押したら確定
Even Nico is sure of this too.Press the switch and it will be confirmed.
でいや窓もいいななんか不気味
Well, the windows are nice too, but it's kind of creepy.
で夢にも怖かったもん
And I was scared even in my dreams
な他はあ羊
Others are sheep
ねここまだできてないよ誰か作ってもいい
It's not done yet. Someone can make it for me.
ぞこれ謎これ
This is a mystery.
すごい
amazing
はあな感じか帰り
I feel like going home
ますはい
Masuhai
ほんじゃあなんか教会案内してくれるって人がいたからまとっか
Actually, there was someone who offered to show me around the church, so I guess it's okay.
な待ちますいやでも下部分はもマジで密集してん
I'll wait, but the bottom part is really crowded.
な
Na
3だから下部分の探索はもうね1日じゃ不
3, so we can't explore the lower part in one day.
可能がすぎてマジで圧巻だよだから視野とかをさほら
It's so possible that it's truly amazing, so look at your field of vision.
こうするとやばいしょり言っちゃうからやんない
If you do this, you'll end up saying something dangerous, so don't do it.
けどこぐらいにし
But at least this much
[音楽]
[music]
てあ教会の人は
Oh, the church people
案内してくれないと僕どこだかわかんないよ
I won't know where I am unless you show me around.
え美術館の真下の方にレストランがあってその直直下に隠すように途端の廃墟に行っ
There was a restaurant right below the museum, and I went to the ruins right below it to hide it.
てくださいはいはいはいはい美術館
Please, yes, yes, museum
があれかあれの
is that or that
マスタここら辺にある
The master is around here
らしいどこ
Where is it like?
だいやこれもよく作ってくれた
Well, you made this well too.
よこういう同じものをたくさん作ってくれる人がいなければ企画が成り立たない
If there are no people who can make a lot of the same thing, the project won't work.
から助かってるよもっと壁一面に作ってくれた
Thank you very much for making it all over the wall.
前これ
Previously this
かこれ単純いやこれすごいないやこの階段作んの結構大変なんだ
It's simple, it's amazing, it's quite difficult to make these stairs.
よ特殊なブロックだからめっちゃ
It's a special block so it's really
ずれるえでもここら辺だよな
It's around here even if it's off.
多分どこだもっと上の方か
Maybe somewhere higher up?
な同じ壁の面にあります1周目の配信でいらしてくれていたお
It's on the same wall.
店
shop
ですどこだ
Where is it?
レストランレストラン
restaurant restaurant
レストランあこれじゃないもんねだって
It's not like that restaurant.
下の方廃墟があっ[音楽]
There are ruins at the bottom [music]
てやば見つから
I can't find it
ない松屋あっ
No Matsuya ah
てえ美術館ってここだよなこの美術館のだよ
This is where the art museum is. This is the museum.
ね今見てた草だらけのところここ
Hey, this is the place I just saw full of grass.
かそれとも
Or maybe
こっち誰れださ探すのがねむずいわ
I'm sleepy trying to figure out who's here.
下が生えてるところあこれか
Is this where the bottom grows?
[音楽]
[music]
な同じ面同じ面ってことはこっちかあこれじゃ
The same side, the same side means this or that.
ね多分これだ
Maybe this is it
これでも見たよねここのレストランこのおしゃれレストラン見
You've already seen this restaurant. You've seen this stylish restaurant.
たこれの
Takore's
近くこれ
This is coming soon
かえ違うよ
It's a different color
なあれどれた全然
I'm not sure what to do
ああんなにかもしかして案内してくれるのかどっか
I wonder if someone will guide me like that?
分かる
I understand
こっち
here
こっちあこれこれ
This, this, this, this.
かじゃ見ます
I'll watch Kaja
え
picture
はいもうとんでもないもん作ってんな何これ
Yes, you're making something outrageous, what is this?
ダークソウルじゃんえあのアルロンだえあ
It's Dark Souls, it's Arron.
えバールデットなしでいや正面入り口地味すぎてわかんないっ
No, the front entrance is so plain that I don't understand it without Ebardet.
て
hand
ワールドエディットのしでよくやったな
You did a great job with World Edit.
すごミニストーリーありえ美術官加法レストランに隠された途端のボロ屋
Awesome mini-story: A dilapidated shop hidden in a restaurant
にてえ先に見ていい
You can watch it first
のすご
Noisy
教会ってかもう城城だ
A church is like a castle.
よじゃあ見る
Okay, let's see
か美術館の下のレストランに隠された途端のボロやはあ
Or the rags hidden in the restaurant under the museum.
はん行きますかまたとんでもないもん作ったな
Okay, let's go. You made something outrageous again.
それ
that
がこれ[音楽]
This is it [music]
かレストランのあ違うこれかレストラン
This or that restaurant is different from this restaurant.
の途端のボロ
rags on the verge of
屋多分これだなここら辺だこれか
It's probably this one, around here, this one.
な違うか
What's wrong?
な途端ここら辺だと思うんだけど
I think it's around here.
なこれラーメンや途端のボロ
What is this ramen and the ridiculous amount of ramen?
やレストランの真下だもんなレストランこれでしょあこれだ絶対これ
It's right below the restaurant.This is the restaurant.This is it.This is definitely this.
だ[音楽]
da [music]
これだ
This is it
おお誰かの死体だもうなんか見慣れたこの街
Oh, it's someone's dead body. This town feels familiar.
で見慣れてしまったから
Because I'm used to seeing it
なあったさあまた何かが始まろうとしているえようやくこの地に到着したこのここ
Hey, something is about to begin again. We've finally arrived here.
数年我が国との関係性は悪化していたがどうにかこの地の人間にも我が神の教えを
The relationship with Japan has been deteriorating for several years, but somehow we have managed to share the teachings of our God with the people of this land.
伝えたい突き刺さる視線の厳しさは今はまだ仕方ないものとして需要するまずは
The harshness of the piercing gaze that I want to convey is something that can't be helped for now, so I demand it first.
かつての有効国だった時代にこの地に入植したものの子孫たちを
The descendants of those who settled this land when it was once a valid nation.
探そう伝え聞く話ではそれはそれは立派な大聖堂を建立しているとのことだ探して
Let's look for it.According to what we've heard, it's said that they're building a magnificent cathedral.
見つからぬ通りはあるまい懸念すべきは違法を後において正当なる競技が出して
There is no such thing as a street where you can't find it, and what is worrying is that legitimate competitions are taking place after the illegal ones.
いる可能性だ私が是正しなければ訂正しなければなる前が彼らの信仰心そのもの
There is a possibility that if I do not correct it, their faith itself will be corrected.
までを否定することのないようあくまで音便に進めることを
In order to avoid denying the
心がけるいずれにせよ今日は疲れた軍では飛行機なんてものを飛ばしているがいずれ
In any case, today the tired military is flying airplanes, but eventually
我々民間人も速やかに軽やかに空を飛んで旅ができるのだろう
We civilians will also be able to travel quickly and easily by flying through the sky.
かあ同胞の捜索がまらぬまま日が過ぎていく
Days pass by without a search for my compatriots.
段の聖堂も探せど探せど見つからない我が国への敵は今度に根深いがこちらが懐を
The enemy of our country is deep-rooted this time, but we can't find it even if we search for the Cathedral of the Steps.
開けば次第に応じてくれるそれでも住居の契約や就職といった社会活動になると壁は
However, when it comes to social activities such as housing contracts and employment, there are walls.
大きい手持ちの金が心持なくなってきた流れ着いた廃墟はは虫と隙間かずに襲わ
I've lost all the money I have, and the ruins I've washed up on are attacked by insects.
れるばかりの空間でおよそ安寧とはほど遠いこの町は入植たたえおのためどか
This town, which is far from peaceful and full of people, is a place where people can settle.
困難はいはいはい安物だったのは彼らも同じはずなのになぜ私を排斥するの
It was difficult, yes, yes, it was cheap, but they should be the same, so why are they excluding me?
かロねん血が染み込み読め
Karonen's blood seeps into it and it's readable.
ないようやく我が国の血を引くものに出会っただが彼も同胞のコミュニティには
I finally met someone who has the blood of my country, but he is also not part of the community of my fellow countrymen.
通じていないようだ悲しいことだが現地に同化して生きる彼のことは尊重し
It's sad that he doesn't seem to understand, but I respect him for living assimilated into the local community.
たいかか細いが手がかり解読不能だ近所のラーメ屋があるがその上に
It's tall or thin, but the clues are impossible to decipher.There's a ramen shop in the neighborhood, but there's a sign on top of it.
スナックだスナックだかバーだかの店があるらしいその天使が我が国の血を引く者
The angel who seems to have a shop selling snacks and bars is of Japanese descent.
たちの顔役とのことだった明日彼女を訪れてみよう
Let's visit her tomorrow as she is said to be the face of our company.
おに天使に接触することはできたが彼女はあくまで初期入植者の子孫をコミュニティ
Although she was able to contact Oni Angel, she was only a community of descendants of early settlers.
の仲間とみなしているようだヒントはくれたものの何回竜の橋の下大口の巨人
He seems to think of him as a member of the group, but he gave me hints about how many times he met the giant with a large mouth under the bridge of the dragon.
見つめる先よりひありをえ
Thank you for everything you look at
あヒトだなあメモした文章を見返しても意味が
Oh man, even when I look back at the sentences I wrote down, there's no meaning to them.
分からない龍といえば巨大な顔の無事を見かけた覚えがある
Speaking of unknown dragons, I remember seeing a giant face intact.
がやだやくたどり着いただが大聖堂の中は人の気配もなく不気味の静寂に満ちている
I arrived quickly, but the inside of the cathedral was filled with an eerie silence, with no sign of anyone.
あんな場所に隠されていたのは両国の両国の関係を思えば弾圧されていたの
Considering the relationship between the two countries, what was hidden in such a place was being suppressed.
だろう家に帰ってから思い出したが多くの場合聖堂には地下が設けられるといううん
After returning home, I remembered that in many cases, cathedrals have an underground section.
えは地下にこもって祈りを捧げていたのかもしれない私の叔父がよくしていたよう
He may have been hiding in the basement and praying, just like my uncle used to do.
に筆が重く感じる怒りとも悲しみともつかぬ感情を文字に転化して気を紛らわす他
In addition to distracting myself by converting the feelings that cannot be described as anger or sadness into words, which I feel as if my pen is heavy.
ない現地の集合と信仰と集合し変化することは世界中よくある話で私もそれは十分
It is a common story all over the world that local gatherings and beliefs change as a result, and I am fully aware of this as well.
承知していたがこれはいくらなんでもあまりに宿悪
I knew this, but this is too much of an evil thing.
だ我が神への苦労イナそれ以前の問題だ思想の違いなどなどといった言葉で納得
It's my struggle with God, it's a problem before that, and I'm satisfied with words like differences in ideology.
できようか彼らはやがていつかおしい犠牲者を見出すだろう羊がどうだとかわけの
Maybe someday they'll find a good victim. What about the sheep?
わからない話をされたがろなものではなさそうだ
I don't think he wants to be told something he doesn't understand.
うん地下白いバラの裏に視界が
Yeah, there's a field of vision behind the white rose underground
赤いう
red
えっとまずひりえだからでもこれ見つけたんだよ
Well, first of all, I found this just because it's Hirie.
な
Na
きっと多分だ
Probably probably
けど竜の
But the dragon
大口でえ巨人巨人の見つめる先ひり
A giant with a big mouth The giant stares at the tip
の
of
ひりえじゃ僕ずるして見つけたの
Hirie, I cheated and found it.
かでここにあるとずっと見つからなかった教会
A church that I couldn't find for a long time when it was here.
がここにあったん
was here
だすごいな地
What an amazing place
か地下いやでも地下への
Or underground, or underground.
入り口それっぽいものはないな
There's nothing like the entrance.
白い
white
バ怪しいのはここら辺
Here's what's weird
かなんかどうにかしたら行けると
Somehow I can go
かゾの裏側さあて謎解き
Behind the scenes, solve the mystery
だ探すぞみんな
Let's look for it, everyone.
いやせっかくだから飛ばないで
No, it's a big deal, so don't fly away
探そうあ大口の巨人
Let's look for the giant with a big mouth
ってどうもさんの
That's Mr.
ことまずは上に行って
First of all, go upstairs
みようわすご
Let's see it
よし
Okay
あまこう
Amakou
かとおでもあれだななかったな
It wasn't Katoomoore.
どっかに地下の入り口があるはずなんだがあ探すのも醍醐だから
There's got to be an underground entrance somewhere, but finding it is the fun part.
ないやすごいよ本当
No, it's amazing, really
にないねやっぱ中からかなえこのさすごく
Kanaeko is amazing from the inside.
ないすごいよ装飾
Not a great decoration
がすごいな何[音楽]
What's amazing? [Music]
あれ読み直すかあ本持ってきた頼むあ本
Should I read that again? I brought a book, please.
あるないかそうだよなあの卒しかないもんなちょっと待っ
I guess that's true. There's no other way than that. Wait a minute.
てろえでもなんかヒントなかったよ
Teroe didn't give me any hints.
なそれといった
That's what I said
ヒントちょ今回こそ僕ちゃんと1人で探す
Hint, this time I'll search by myself
わちょっと借りるわちょこの本あのおしおし
I'm going to borrow a little bit of this book, that punishment.
みんなマウスのコロコロをぎゅってやるとねコピーできる
If you roll your mouse hard enough, you can copy it.
からホビーし
From hobby
たこれを見ながら
While looking at Takore
やろう
let's do it
さて街かのところこれはもう見つけ
Well, I already found this somewhere in town.
たうんうんうん制度に地下がけられというえでも地下のヒント別にないもんなあ
Even if you say that the underground system is being destroyed, I don't think there are any hints about the underground.
白いバラの裏に白いバラの
A white rose behind a white rose
裏白いバを
The white background
探そうこれじゃないよねこれは
Let's look for this, isn't this?
違うやっぱ花なんだ花を探そうこれだ多分これ
No, it's a flower after all. Let's look for a flower. This is probably this.
だよ来た白い
It's here, white
バラ白い花あれ
Rose, white flower
はあこれも白いバラだ
Ha, this is also a white rose.
なあったあったあったあったあったあったあったあっ
There was, there was, there was, there was, there was, there was.
たこれでどこが開いたん
Where did this open?
だ向こうも
And the other side too
ある
be
これだけかこれでどこかが開いたんじゃない
Isn't this all or this something opened?
かあ
Kaa
すごよし引きます
It's amazingly good
[音楽]
[music]
う
cormorant
ここで祈りを捧げてい
I'm praying here
た
Ta
で視界が赤い何してたんだ
So what were you doing when your vision was red?
よしかもほら他の像と違って色が黒ずんでる
Okay, but unlike the other statues, the color is darker.
ホラーだったやっぱり斧があっ[音楽]
It was horror, but there was an ax [music]
て羊の部屋似てるね同じ儀式だったんか
It looks similar to the sheep room. Was it the same ritual?
なやっぱすごいなえ他ないよ
Wow, that's amazing. There's nothing else like it.
ね他何かが隠されてるとかはないよ[音楽]
There's nothing else hidden [music]
ねや空間よく作った
You made a good space
な以上ですいや
That's all.
ありがとうマジですごいわこれのギミックもすごい
Thank you, this is seriously amazing. This gimmick is also amazing.
しあ閉じてる閉じ
It's closed. It's closed.
てる
Teru
よし
Okay
じゃあま最後に影も入れる
Okay, let's add a shadow at the end.
か影も入れ
Also include shadows
て周り見て終わりにしよっかな本当になんか1週間でよくやるよみんな
I guess I'll just look around and call it a day. I'm really going to do a lot of things in a week, everyone.
マジでセルカボックスもねなんか開けなかっ
Seriously, I can't even open the selfie box.
た
Ta
わプロが多すぎるでねこの配信見て僕も何か作りたいっていう人がいたら下の概要
There are too many producers, so if anyone sees this stream and wants to make something, please see the summary below.
欄のねGoogleフームからID送ってく
I'll send you the ID from Google Hoom in the column.
くさいID送ってくれたらホワイトリストにね追加しますのでよろしくお願いします
If you send me your bad ID, I will add it to the whitelist. Thank you.
でID送ったのに入れないって人がいたらおそらく
If someone can't get in even though I sent them their ID, it's probably
あのIDが違う可能性がありますのでちゃんとねマイクラ内のIDを送って
There is a possibility that that ID is different, so please be sure to send your Minecraft ID.
くださいすごいって白[音楽]
Please, it's amazing! White [Music]
これナイスもちゃんとしてたしね
This is nice and done properly
かっこいいガチですごい
It's really cool and amazing
なマジですごいよ
It's seriously amazing
これということで皆さん今回はこれにて終わりにさせていただきます
With this, everyone, I will end this article here.
え来週でマイクラマイクラ差は1ヶ月ですま1か月だからで言って何かをするわけで
Eh, the difference between Minecraft and Minecraft will be one month next week. Just because it's one month doesn't mean we're going to do anything.
もなく多分また紹介するかと思いますが今後ともね好きな時間に入って好きな建築
I'll probably introduce it again soon, but from now on, I'll be able to take advantage of my free time and introduce my favorite architecture.
をしてで本当になんか周りのね方の建築物にね経緯を払って建築していただければ
If you could actually build it with due consideration to the surrounding buildings.
どんな建築をしても構いませんのでよろしくお願いし
I don't care what kind of architecture you want, so I'd appreciate your help.
ます僕もね一応毎日ログインして何かしらのものは作っているのでただえチャットに
Me too, I log in every day and create something, so I'm just going to chat.
は配信外以外では反応できませんのでそこだけよろしくお願いし
I can't respond outside of the broadcast, so please only respond there.
ますそんな感じで今日はこれにて終わりにさせていただきたいと思いますご視聴
With that in mind, I would like to end today with this.
ありがとうございました紹介してくださった方えいつも作ってくださってる方
Thank you to the person who introduced me and the person who always makes it.
ありがとうございますマナー守ってねとても嬉しいですということでえー明日は
Thank you very much, please respect your manners. I'm very happy. So, tomorrow.
心霊写真です心霊写真を久しぶりに見たいと思いますまた夜お会いしましょう以上
It's a ghost photo. I'd like to see a ghost photo for the first time in a while. See you again tonight.
ですお疲れ
Thank you for your hard work
様おっとチャンネル登録高評価Twitterのフォローとアーカイブに
Subscribe to Samootto channel, follow and archive highly rated Twitter
感想コメントよろしくお願いし
Thank you for your feedback and comments
ます
Masu